こんにちは
これはジョン・グリーンヴィッチの記録です
プロメーテウス株式会社で、生理学者として
プロジェクト・パンドーラーの為に働いています
あのー
ここにいるのは、まだ信じられませんわ
なんか、これは給料のことではなく・・・
優先度２のプロジェクトのために働くことです
装備は桁外れ、可能は・・・
これこそ最高のレベルの科学です
ここにいることなんて、超嬉しいです
21日
このヴィールスは私たちに
まだ謎です
突然変異が早いし、
感染性も強いし
解毒剤はどうやって
開発できるのですか?
況してやみんなのために
合成するなんて
幹部は、もちろん特に
嬉しくなかったが、
売り上げの減少にもかかわらず、
私たちは優先度１に高まったんです
すなわち、このプロジェクトに
お金はより多くなりました
これは少し助かると希望してます
47日
解毒剤への一歩
進んだが、
行くべき道はまだ
長いです
ヴィールスは
突然変異したり
DNAの構成を何度も
変更したりして
そして解毒剤は？
解毒剤は精密的にDNAの構成に
合わなければならないことです
すなわち、我々は、
決して、解毒剤を
予め作るのは
できるわけないです
まだまだ道は長いです
84日
We have taken a great step forward
Anderson perfected the antidote
I believe, with the right DNA coding,
we can stop the virus
The management was impressed
but not impressed enough
They have transferred him
No money for research, they say
And since when does a Priority One
project become short of money?
98日
The working climate is strained
McRich just quit
without another word
And Anderson?
Disappeared without a trace
No one knows anything
Well, I could imagine
they have fired him
after the trouble he made
but why does nobody know anything?
Seems as though I am the only
one left working on Pandora
103日
Today I received an anonymous letter
containing only a
micro SD card
The data encrypted
I think, they are...
from the... laboratory
Someone passed Pandora's
documents to me
McRich perhaps? What if they
want to silence him?
Maybe I'm getting paranoid but
isn't it a strange coincidence
that Anderson had this...
accident at this precise moment?
I need to watch out whom I trust
116日
Section seven has been closed
Lacking money, they say
Project Pandora?
Project Pandora discontinued
for ever
all recordings deleted
but why deleting all documents
when discontinuing a project?
I've been transferred
Priority Four
Well and today's question is:
What goes wrong when a virologist
suddenly has to research on hay fever?
Let's find it out
120日
My inquiries to the management
attract attention
Just now in the corridor
Wilhemsen himself asked me
to stop nosing around
He said he could not guarantee
my safety any more
Whatever that may mean?
Let's find it out
123日
My last
Asking questions became
quite unpleasant
I'm being... watched...
My telephone's tapped
My apartment...
Someone broke into my apartment
I've put the SD card to
a save place and ehm...
Maybe I'm becoming paranoid but
I've got the feeling, that this is...
the only reason why I...
why nothing has happened to me yet
Well who knows...
以上です